upfront group
It's time for another episode of Upgami. This time we will be talking with Akari Takeuchi of Angulum and Yumeno Kishimoto of Tsubaki Factory.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
So, first of all, let's take a look behind the scenes of the two MCs.
Yes, I'm Akari Takeuchi.
I, Akari Takeuchi, have a new single coming out on June 14,
I will be releasing two A-side singles, "Ai no Kedamono" and "Doukunin",
This "Ai no Kedamono" was really hard work.
The dance was really difficult,
I could never dance to that one.
It was really amazing. I couldn't physically do it anymore, and when I was a freelance dancer in the beginning, I couldn't even dance.
And it took me a long time to make it my own, so we all did it together.
So, I said, "Let's do intervals," and it was almost like a club activity.
We would dance as fast as we could, take a minute off, start the music right after a minute, do it again, take a break, do it one more time, and then we were done.
Three sets, and it was really the hardest thing I had ever done.
You did a menu like that?
Yes, I was surprised.
I really felt like I was in an athletic club at school.
It was the last single, wasn't it?
Last single. That's why it was so hard, so it didn't feel like a last single at all.
You left behind something amazing.
I was really surprised myself. I didn't expect the last song to be this intense.
It's cool.
I really hope that if you haven't seen it yet, you should see it.
I will watch it a lot.
I hope you will.
I, Kishimoto, have been practicing writing my own lyrics and songs recently, and I've even performed a little bit at some events,
I'm a bit biased, because most of the songs I write seem to be cute, and I guess I grew up in the Hello Project, but there's something a little matured about them.
I want to make songs that are a little bit more mature, that seem to be good at jazz or something, but I'd rather make cute songs in the idol style, like Matsuura E's debut.
I tend to make cute idol-type songs, like when E Matsuura made her debut.
So I decided to study various genres of music one more time so that I can make various kinds of songs.
I've been trying to listen to various kinds of music. Someday I hope to be able to
I hope to be able to showcase my music to many people somewhere.
I will do my best.
Let's start off with this up-coming album,
Morning Musume。 23 new member lesson video.
Please take a look at the lesson video of the two new members of Morning Musume。 23 new members.
They passed the exam.
Congratulations!
They have decided to join as Morning Musume。ヌs 17th term members.
They have passed.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
It has been decided that you will join Morning Musume。
re.
Please open one more line.
Oh no.
WABE MIBOMU
Wabe Mibomu
Brace
Brace.
Yes, you're right.
I'm going to mic this now and listen to your voice.
Three, yes.
MAMELI BOMB
MAMELIBOMB.
Mameribom.
Yeah.
Behind the Breath
MAMELI BOMB
Yes, open the side
Left hand side up.
MAMELIBOMB
Mamelibom.
Mameribombs.
Mameribombs
Mamelibombs
By raising his hand
I raised my breath so my voice went up
I got the high part
You have to raise your exhale
Yes, sir.
Not straight up, but to the side.
To the side. - Yes, sir.
MAMELIBOMB.
Rest.
Right hands, each other's right hands.
Mameribom.
You can be as creative as you want.
Mr. White.
I can't raise it. I'm holding the microphone.
No, you can be creative.
Here you go.
Mameri bomb.
Okay, next one's a little higher.
Mameribom.
Yes, a little longer.
And you sing the low note all the way down.
Three, yes.
Mabemi Bob.
Mabemi bob.
I don't lower it.
Always like this.
Open mouth
Breath.
Yes, yes.
Yes, very good.
Leave the instrument as it is.Please leave the instruments as they are.
I'm going to go ahead and say "Aa".
Uh-oh.
How do you put the logon in?
You have to do it like you're swallowing.
Uh-oh.
Connect.
One more time.
Woah.
Yes, the last one.
One last time.
Woah.
You're supposed to say it like this.
Blister, blister, blister, blister.
How's that?
Right there at the end.
Blister, blister, blister, blister...
There, there, there, there.
Blister, blister, blister, blister.
There you go.
It's going down one piece, just like this.
It's like this.
There you go.
Blister, blister, blister, blister.
Blister, blister, blister, blister
Blister blister blister blister
Yes, Breath
Yes, it's coming, Breath
Okay, let's sing the song.
I'll play the piano once
One, two, three, four...
You're supposed to be aware of that.
No one.
Please take the phrase of the song with your left hand.
One, two, three, four, five.
I won't let anyone notice.
Okay, Inoue-san.
Look at your left hand.
Do something about that unmotivated left hand.
I won't let anyone notice.
Cold feelings.
Is it working now?
Do you think you did it, or don't you think you did it, or don't you think you did it?
I didn't do it myself. I didn't do it to anyone.
I'm not asking anyone to be surprised.
I want to make them notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice, notice...
2002 Concerta Smoke, now.
I'm bending over so hard right now.
I don't want to make anyone or anyone notice or notice anything I don't want to make anyone or anyone notice anything
Yes, sing like you do now
Even in your day-to-day life, you can't do it now.
Even if I love you
Yes, now tell me how you feel
Don't let anyone else think they know how you feel
Then I won't feel like I know how you feel
Next time, I'll ask you to let me know so I don't have to search for it.
Okay, I'll end with your voice.
It was difficult, and even though I thought I was doing it, I often wasn't.
I thought I should break my calories more and add not only my voice but also my movements together.
If I keep up with it, it will expand, won't it?
I can go anywhere.
I can have as many as I want like this now.
I can have it around here.
Dah! Dah!
Dah!
I'll give you this.
Woe.
Woe!
Way.
Listen to the sound.
Whoo-hoo!
One, two.
Woe.
Woe, woe, woe, woe.
Yeah, that war will stop it once.
Way, way, way, way.
Stop! Stop it! Stop this!
Keep singing.
One, two, three, four, five.
I won't let anyone notice
I've lost my mind
Bring it back one more time
Hold it, one, two, three, four, five
I won't let anyone notice
Rustling feelings
I'm with you.
Yes. Three, two, one.
I'm not gonna let anyone see that.I won't let anyone find out.
I don't need feelings right now.
I don't need to feel right now.
I don't need emotion right now.
Let's just practice a little bit of what that means.
One, two, three, four, five.
I'm not gonna let anyone notice.
I'm not going to let anyone notice.
I'm alone
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Still, I'd come right up to someone
Someone innocent and wicked
I was joking around and I didn't give a shit
I'm just trying to be nice
That's not the truth
That's the truth.
It's not there.
There's no there there's no there's no there's no there's no there.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
3, yes
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
Belly up, three, yes.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
And then you're gonna get this sound in your chest voice.
Okay, three, yes.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
Do it! How's your hip? I'm on three, yes.
You're practicing your hip lift. Three, yes.
Well, I'm actually going to go for it.
I'd like to be able to use the rechest breast, but I'm not doing it right now.
I'm not sure I'm doing it right now.
I don't know what to do with this sound that I'm modifying today.
Right now.
But then...
One, two, three, four, five.
But that's it...
I'm around here.
That's when the shape of the note goes from my head to my body, and my body feels it before my head feels it, and it takes it to the top.
Then it's my voice.
That's how I make my voice there.
What you need to practice before the next session is
Practice in nanana.
What happens when you sing datum in nanana?
One, two, three, four, chet chet chet chet
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
And you know what, it's not a smooth tango race.
Nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna
If you make it a tango race of nanna like this...
One, two, three, four, hoi
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah
That's nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
Nanna nanna nanna nanna
na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
The one where you can only stand on your toes
One, two, three, four, five
Nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna
If you can stretch out like a nah-nah-nah-nah-nah-nah then the song will change.
Okay? Emotions can't just be done with the mind.
It's an emotion because it's coming from the body.
Nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna
Nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna nanna
Nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan-nan.
Yes, so that was a spitch off.
Thank you very much.
You taught me a lot of things that I have never experienced before.
It was really an exciting day with a lot to learn!
Thank you very much.
I really couldn't do anything.
I will definitely do what I did in today's lesson
I want to practice everything at home so that I can do it before the next lesson.
The quality of the lesson I'm looking for was not at all what I was looking for today.
I couldn't do it at all today, to be honest.
The bow getter was kind of...
I think it's better if we can talk about it physically.
I could talk to them with my body.
I can really feel their animal-like nature.
I think it's easy to pull them along.
So, if you give them a little push from behind
If you give them a little push from behind
I could see that she can explore on her own.
I could see that.
And as for the dog food...
I don't know how to say it.
She's very, very nervous.
I don't know what to call it.
I've never been here before.
I know you've never been here before, but...
I don't know if I can make any assumptions.
There's something that stuck in my mind during the lesson.
There is something that sticks with me in the lesson.
And by "stuck," I mean stuck in a good way.
I think there's still something hidden inside this person.
I feel like he doesn't know how to let it out.
I get the feeling that he doesn't know how to let it out yet.I get the feeling that you don't know yet.
I don't even know what I'm not doing.
I think maybe today...
After this lesson, when I look back by myself
I did that, I did that, I did that.
I wonder why I couldn't do that.
I think she'll think about it.
I had a feeling she was like that.
It's not that she didn't listen.
It's not that she's unmotivated.
She's doing a lot of input.
But her output is still a little bit lacking.
On the other hand, that inability to output is what makes it interesting.
On the other hand, when it erupts...
I wonder if when it erupts, we will discover a very interesting child.
I was thinking that when it erupts, we'll discover a very interesting child.
So, I've seen the video of the new member's lesson, and I've heard that Morning Musume。 23, 17-year-old Haruka Inoue, a sophomore in high school, and 14-year-old Haruka Bow, a junior high school student, are the new members of Morning Musume
And Ayako Yumi-Shimoda, a 14-year-old junior high school student, has joined as a new member.
I watched the video of their exciting lesson, and I wondered what their first lesson was like.
I was in the 4th or 5th grade at the beginning of my first lesson, so I don't remember much about it.
I don't even remember the first lesson, but I was wondering how I would be able to express myself as a member of Morning Musume。 I'm really looking forward to see how they will polish their expressive ability and how they will change as a member of Morning Musume。
I'm really looking forward to seeing how they will polish their expressive ability as a member of Morning Musume and how they will change. KishimotoMy first voice training singing lesson was during the audition for Morning Musume。 I remember now, it was a lip roll.
I remember now, I couldn't even do a lip roll. I couldn't even do that. I couldn't even do a lip roll. I was at that level, practicing all night long.
But I started out not being able to do it at all. But I desperately tried my best, and I was able to make it to this wonderful group of seniors, all of whom have wonderful voices.
I am sure that I will become a person with a wonderful singing voice. I am sure that this will happen, so I would like to encourage all the new members of the various teams to work hard and do their best.
That's all for now. 23 new member lesson video.
Angulum Ai no Kedamono June 14, Onsai Ion
Let's work hard together!
Next up, here it is: Beyonds Yomeshinai Yozora ni Yume no Dakudanai Yozora ni Musical instrument recording.
Here's a look at the recording of the wind instruments for Beyonds' latest single, "Yume to Dorenai Yozora no Yozora ni" (I Can't Even Draw a Dream).
Yes, I don't think we can do the whole thing at once,
We would like you to proceed with the recording where it is easy to cut it,
I'd like to make a request for you.
I'm going to make a request.
I won't let you do that.
Even if you don't want me to.
Why are you remembering this?
I'm remembering this?
If there's nothing there...
I wonder.
What are you here to do?
There is no reason why anyone would want to
There is no reason
I feel like there is no reason.
La-la-la-la-la...
The world is a culling of oysters
the world of life
If we lose
I will not graduate.
Thank you very much.
As for the overall flow itself
I think it's already pretty good.
I think the rest is in the details.
I would be happy to give you my request for the details.
The first part where the tempo is slow.
Intro 1 and so on.
The part before the so-called intro 2
If possible
A little more exaggerated.
For example, vibrato.
Like the bath...
A bit more of a push and pull on the peaks and valleys.
Like a push and pull
I would be grateful if you could make it more exaggerated.
I would be very grateful if you could take it in the direction where the
Then we moved on to 3C.
The song itself will start to take on a more big-band
I would be grateful if you could take it in a direction where the "push and pull" is more exaggerated.
I wanted to change the atmosphere of the song
I also wanted to change the atmosphere of the music
I wanted to change the atmosphere from the brass band image to a little bit more of a groovy one, including the horns.
I'd like to take the groove and intonation in the direction of a bit more fun, even if it's a little rough rather than tight, from 3C onwards
I'd like you to play it from 3C onwards until the full ending.
Thank you for watching.
You were smiling little by little.
Your smile is melting away little by little.
Thank you.
Little by little, you smiled.
Your smile. Little by little, it's melting away.
Thank you.
Little by little, you smiled.
Your smile, little by little
Your smile... Little by little... It's melting away.
Thank you.
Let me modify the intro to sound a little weaker, about a piano .
Music
Excellent.
Ladies and gentlemen, since we are going in at 97, I will take it out at 93, four before that.
Melody you like, humming along
You like the melody, you like the melody, you like the melody, you like the melody, you like the melody, you like the melody
I'm humming the melody you like
I'm humming the melody that you like
The melody that you like to sing
As you, I've been wrapped up in something wonderful
Inside the world that I learned with youYou and I, in the world that we remember
We'll be friends We'll be friends
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
I originally dug it. 3B107-108 and two bars, please.
I'll hold it all, inside the world beyond the stars
Yes, thank you. I'll take it out from 3C4, just in case.
Please.
4 bars before 3C, please.
Yes, thank you. 3C4 in advance.
Yes, thank you.
It's magnificent, isn't it? It's magnificent. The Beyoncés are very expressive, and they sing a lot of songs, but their voices alone are very expressive, and with these instruments, the quality of the music is multiplied hundreds and thousands of times. The world view.
When I saw it live, it was like watching a parade, and I thought it was a wonderful song.
Just watching it made me smile, and it was fun, too,
I could really feel the emotion, the power, and the power of the recording, so I thought it was really wonderful.
That's all I have to say about the Beyoncès, "I can't even draw a dream in the night sky" instrumental recording.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure something good will come out of it.
Upcame by Akari Takeuchi of Angulum and Yumeno Kishimoto of Tsubaki Factory. Here's the next one.
Rehearsal footage of the event celebrating the 25th anniversary of Mari Yasuzaki Yaguchi's debut.
Please take a look at the rehearsal of Mari Anzaki Yaguchi's 25th anniversary event held on May 26 at Tokyo Aima Show.
Good morning.
Sorry for the delay. Sorry for the delay.
One person is at the bottom. Please take good care of him.
Sorry about the butt.
It's your first time, isn't it?
First time.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, it is.
Yes, it is.
You weren't born yet.
Some of us.
Is that so?
How about Momochan?
I was born in 26 years.
26 years?
I graduated.
I look forward to working with you.
Please take care of me.
Please do.
The three of you want to come to the front while singing, and Mr. Yaguchi takes a step back.
This singer, yes.
The three of you come closer, 0.5, 0.5.
In the triangle here, a little more in front is okay.
Yes, I'll keep it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Thoughts?
Oh, yeah.
I hope it's not choreography.
Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
Can I dance?
I'm so nervous.
Who are you three?
Let's see..,
One, two, three, four.
Three, four.
Five,
This way.
The other way.
Four. Five,
Six,
Six. Seven,
Seven,
Eight,
On 1,
You may use 8 and the next count of 1 to make any pose you wish.
Yes, sir.
The members in the back,
Of the characharacharacharacharacharachanchanchan,
using the three sounds of characharacharacharacharacharacharacharacharacharacharacharacharachan,
They come to the three sides like this,Since they come in like this on the third side,
For the second eight, you can all stay almost exactly as you are.
Stay in the pose.
Five, six, seven, eight,
Those who came like this,
I'd like you to do it as you are,
Then, a little bit,
I'll ask them to come forward a couple of steps.
Then, the third eight will come forward and take about two steps.
And then, the third one,
Bend your knees a little,
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
And hands like this.
I want you to do it in a sexy way.
Three, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
It's cooler if the elbows are taut,
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Yes.
Smile, smile, smile, smile,
Use that chancha-cha-cha-cha sound,
Chancha, chancha, wave.
Chancha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha, like this, your hand.
Like this,
And then, your feet, like this,
Take a step forward.
Yes.
That's cool.
It's amazing.
Chang-chang, chang-chang, and so on,
After stabilizing,
Yes.
Like this,
Close this hand once,
Yes.
Chang-chang.
Whoa, whoa.
All right, just like that, just like you like it.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-chang.
Open the legs.
Zip, zip.
A little bit diagonal here.
It's unison.
Yes.
In unison.
That was a game up, wasn't it?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Please do.
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Wow.
Thank you for your hard work.
Well, it was a little bit, it was the first day of rehearsal.
Well, but it's only today.
It's only today.
It's the only day.
Yes, it is. I feel like we're ready to go to the show now,
By the time this is playing, the event has already taken place.
That's right.
Well, you all know the result.
I wonder if I will be able to dance well in the show.
I wonder. How was it?
How did it go?
I'm sure you made it on time.
Yes, I think so.
I'm thinking, yes. I hope so.
Also, we sang and danced Summer Nights Town this time.
Hirayu-chan newly choreographed the interlude,
Hirayu-chan put together a new choreography for the interlude.
It was amazing.
It was really cool.
The choreography was not too difficult, as requested,
I asked for a choreography that wasn't too difficult and looked cool,
It was a crazy request, but they made it come true,
And they did it in a way that made us feel united, and made us stand on our feet.
It was wonderful, really.
We also sang a lot of other songs,
We sang a lot of other songs, and the event will be archived.
So, even if you couldn't make it on the day of the event, we will be archiving the event,
If you were not able to attend the event and would like to see the event, please go to the archive.
Please take a look.
I really want you to see it.
I really want you to see Hirayu-chan's choreography,
Please don't miss it.
I'm not sure if I'm dancing cool enough.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
If you don't dance well in the performance, I would like you to reshoot the archive one more time.
I really want you to reshoot it.
I'm scared.
I'll give it one shot, and I'll do my best.
It's already wonderful.
It's wonderful, and I feel like I'm not allowed to see something like this.
Really.
I used to watch them on TV when I was little,
I used to watch Morning Musume。 I was a little girl watching Morning Musume on TV,
I didn't expect it to be the undiluted solution related to the second place,I don't think so,
I thought it was nice,
I thought it was nice.
I thought it was very valuable.
I am a 2nd term member of S/mileage, and Rina Katsuta, who is in the same term as me, was on the stage with me,
That's something like that!
It's not every day you get a chance to perform with your seniors.
I was thinking that I need to become something like Nikki as soon as possible.
I don't think I'll make it.
I really envy you that you have such a great opportunity to perform with us.
I wish I could have been there to see it.
Mao Akiyama is a member of Tsubaki, and she is a very good dancer.
She is a very good dancer and shines in the rehearsal videos.
And Miyo Hirai choreographed it.
The choreography was really cool, too.
So I thought there were a lot of members who were really good at dancing.
But I also thought that there was a side step to the song "Summer Night Town".
But the side-step to this music is like a side-step to this music.
I don't think I can catch up with the original dancers who have danced this song many times before.
I was thinking that I can't catch up with the original dancers who have danced it many times before.
I would like to continue to do my best to catch up with my seniors as an active dancer.
This is the rehearsal video of Mari Yasuzaki Yaguchi's 25th anniversary event.
Beyonce New Single "Seek Me, Fate's Traveler
Now on sale
Thank you for all your hard work
It's time for Akari Takeuchi and Yumeno Kishimoto to say goodbye to Upokami!
I, Kishimoto, have been watching various videos of up-cam, and I've seen them in various combinations, and I've seen them on my cell phone at home, and I've seen them in various combinations, and I've seen them on my cell phone at home.
I'm always watching the videos on my cell phone at home, but I felt I was able to enjoy them twice as much as I usually do.
I realized how important it is to have someone to watch with.
That's wonderful!
So let's continue to watch together at home!
It's the last time you're going to MC today, right?
Yes, I think it's the last one.
I'm glad we could do the last one together, and I made some discoveries, so let's continue to watch it together at home.
Let's watch it together at home from now on.
We'll watch it regularly.
I'd like to watch it on the big screen with the TV connected.
Please do.
I would be surprised if you said it was the last one, but this time there was a video of recording, and this time it was a recording of a joyous instrument, but I was surprised to hear that it was the last one.
I was also able to learn a lot about how our new songs are made through up-cam videos.
I also had a lot of footage of my own recording sessions.
I've become a fan of mine more than I imagined.
I was surprised at the number of people who became my fans after seeing these recording videos.
This is the reason why I became a fan.
That's why I was so happy to be a part of Up-Cami.
It's an important place for you.
Yes, I'm glad.
Thanks to you, I now have the support of so many people.
I'm really grateful for that.
I would like to continue to see the new songs of Ange and the other side of the junior members as a viewer, so please do your best.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
And also this time, I'd like to show you a lesson video of a new member of Morning Musume。 23's new member's lesson was shown on the screen.
Two new members have joined Angelem as well.
We have two new members, Hana Goto and Yukiho Shimoita on the lower board.
Congratulations!
And also JuiceJuice has one member, Mifu Kawashima, who will join JuiceJuice as well.
I'm sure that we will be able to see more and more of our different qualities and momentum from the Hello!
Upcami will be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group. We will introduce you to the parts you don't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time, upcami's partners are Akari Takeuchi of Angulum and Yume Kishimoto of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye.
Next time on Upokami, we'll see Morning Musume。 23 new members' dance lesson,
And,
Beyonce Yume no Yona Kakeru Yozora Ni ni" (In the Night Sky Where Even Dreams Cannot Be Drawn) instrumental recording.
Please look forward to it!
Please subscribe to our channel.